mobilecomputermag.co.uk 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Broadband Genie

###  Personal data, email policy and cookies

#####  _Updated January 27, 2015_

Broadband Genie is committed to respecting the privacy of its visitors. We do not collect any personal data when you visit the site, or vote in polls, and you can access and browse our website without disclosing any personal data. We use cookies which collect anonymous information about the pages visited to allow us to monitor the performance of the website.

If you use our availability checker, Broadband Genie will use your postcode and telephone number to perform a broadband availability check on your line. We do not store your telephone number. We may store your postcode and availability or speed results and other non-personal data for the purpose of building up a national picture of broadband speeds and availability. We may disclose this data to other organisations for similar research purposes; never for sales purposes.

This website does make use of cookies so that your availability information is used throughout your visit. You can read more about cookies, and how to control cookies using your browser settings, at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifying information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide interest-based advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART (Dynamic Advertising Reporting and Targeting) cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

By entering your email address on the Broadband Genie site, including submitting a form or entering a competition, you will be subscribed to our email mailing list about our products, news and promotions. 

We are committed to maintaining your privacy and we will not pass your information to any third party providers. However, we reserve the right to pass your details to law enforcement agencies if required to do so by applicable law, or in cases of possible criminal prosecution.

You can unsubscribe from these emails at any time by following the unsubscribe link in each email that we send out or you can update your preferences about which emails you would like to receive [here](http://email.broadbandgenie.co.uk/k/Genie-Ventures/preference_center_form).
